module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Louie and Huey are grandnephews of what Disney character?', 
    a: 'Donald Duck',
    b: 'Della Duck',
    c: 'Donna Duck',
    d: 'Scrooge McDuck',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Roman numeral "L" stands for what number?', 
    a: '1000',
    b: '5',
    c: '50',
    d: '100',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who composed the score for the 1992 movie, Batman Returns?', 
    a: 'John Williams',
    b: 'Danny Elfman',
    c: 'Hans Zimmer',
    d: 'Howard Shore',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which artist/group has never won a Grammy?', 
    a: 'Guns N\' Roses',
    b: 'Stevie Wonder',
    c: 'Metallica',
    d: 'Eric Clapton',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the periodic table symbol for phosphorus?', 
    a: 'Ps',
    b: 'P',
    c: 'Fe',
    d: 'Ph',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The "arthro" in "arthroplasty" refers to which body parts?', 
    a: 'Core',
    b: 'Genetalia',
    c: 'Joints',
    d: 'Blood Vessels',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What company\'s slogan is "Everywhere You Want to Be"?', 
    a: 'Discover',
    b: 'American Express',
    c: 'Chase',
    d: 'Visa',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who directed the 1982 movie "The Dark Cystal"?', 
    a: 'Jim Henson',
    b: 'Steven Spielberg',
    c: 'James Cameron',
    d: 'George Lucas',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What card game requires one to use up all their cards by forming particular arrangments and sequences?', 
    a: 'Rummy',
    b: 'Blackjack',
    c: 'Poker',
    d: 'Solitaire',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Tiny Tim was famouse for playing what instrument?', 
    a: 'Ukulele',
    b: 'Theremin',
    c: 'Didgeridoo',
    d: 'Kazoo',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];